# 青海·西宁
Xining, Qinghai
# 雪鱼现在还在西宁
Xue Yu is still at Xining
# 今天是起个大早 打算早早地去把早饭吃了
I woke up so early today to have an early breakfast.
# 现在是早上起来六点半 温度呢 只有9度
Now is 6:30 am in the morning, the temperature is 9°C.
# 比我前两天来的 都要冷
colder than the previous two days when I just arrived
# 已经把秋裤套上了
Now I am wearing leggings under my pants (to stay warm).
# 这么清冷的天气 一定要吃点比较硬核的早餐
Such freeze morning, I need to find some rich food as my breakfast
# 像我们之前吃的羊肠面 就是比较富有能量
Like the lamb offal noodle that we ate before, it is high in calories
# 今天呢 再吃个不一样的  就是牛杂汤
Today we are going to try something different: beef offal soup.
# 这家店很小 还不太好找
This café is too small to be easily found.
# 别人都叫它是 巷子里的米其林
People regard it as a Michelin-starred restaurant in a small alley
# 至于为什么会叫这个名字
Why do people call it that name?
# 我觉得应该是有点贵吧
I think it is because the price is a bit high
# 走 去看看吧
Let’s go
# 真是太冷了 我的鼻子都冻红了
I am freezing, my nose is red with cold
# 来的不晚啊 没想到还是有这么多人 比我要早到
It is not too late; I did not expect that so many people came here earlier than me.
# 多少钱一碗
How much for one bowl of soup?
# 有30元 20元的 最少是15元一碗的
(Different types,) 30 or 20 Yuan, and the cheapest one is 15
# 最少15 给我拿一个30的吧 加一个饼
At least 15 Yuan…I will take the one that is 30 Yuan, plus a naan
# 在这儿吃
Dine in？
# 对
Yes
# 每碗是配一个饼
One bowl of soup comes with one naan
# 过去了
Paid.
# 30的是吧
30 Yuan, right?
# 不是的 这是两个小碗的端
Not that one, those are two small bowls
# 这正好来了一锅新汤
Here comes a new pot of soup
# 大哥 20块钱的和30块钱的有什么区别吗
Bro, what is the difference between the 20 Yuan soup and 30 Yuan soup?
# 料是一样的 但是量不一样
The ingredients are the same, but the amounts are different.
# 这个是我的吗
Is that for me?
# 对 30的
Yes, 30 Yuan soup
# 好 谢谢
Ok, thanks
# 到这边吧 那边没有位
Come here! No seats available there.
# 这是我们刚才排队买的牛杂汤
This is the beef offal soup we bought after waiting in a long line
# 奢华 顶配版 30块钱
Luxurious, top-of-the-line, 30 Yuan soup
# 里面的内容 极其丰富
There are so many ingredients in the soup
# 看 像牛肚 牛肉还有切的很大块的牛肠
Look, ox tripe, beef and large pieces of ox intestine
# 先尝一口汤吧
Let’s taste the soup first.
# 哇 被辣到
Wow, the spicy taste gets me.
# 这种辛辣 不仅是胡椒粉的辛辣
This spiciness is not just because of pepper powder
# 还有大葱的辛辣
As well as the pungency of green onion
# 说实话 我从来没有喝过一碗汤 是这个味道
To be honest, it is first time that I eat a beef soup with this kind of flavor
# 有些冲
Sharp taste
# 因为这边的温度 早晚的温度差异很大
Because of the big temperature differences between day and night
# 喝碗这种辛辣的汤 能够去除寒冷
the beef soup with such sharp taste can drive the chill away.
# 让你一早上 暖暖的
Make you warm for the whole morning.
# 味道指数：4颗星
Flavor score: 4 stars
# 这里有一块牛肠
There is a piece of ox intestine.
# 肉其实没有什么特别的味道 就是处理的很干净
No weird smell or strange tastes, the ox intestine is thoroughly cleaned.
# 这碗牛杂的味道 灵魂 全在汤里
The soul of this bowl of beef offal soup is the soup itself.
# 可免费无限加汤
You can add extra soup for free
# 找到一根好肥硕的牛肚
I find such a big piece of ox tripe
# 他们这边的牛杂为什么感觉都是那么的肥美又软烂
Why is the beef offal in the soup so plump and tender？
# 大哥 这边是早上几点开门
Hi bro, what is your opening time?
# 每天早上4点到上午10点半
4:00 am to 10:30 am
# 4点就开门了 这么早
Open at 4:00 am? So early
# 我们过来的时候 已经有等的人了 有的人已经在等着了
When we arrive at the café, there are already many people waiting here
# 像喝完酒的
Like people who just finish drinking
# 通宵的也是 他们都过来吃
Or people who stay up the whole night. They would come to eat.
# 刚从小店出来 店里只有几张桌子 人挤得满满的
We just came out from the café. There are only a few tables, so crowded
# 刚才还是好不容易才找的座位
It took me a while to find the place to sit.
# 好多人也都是一早 赶来吃这碗牛杂汤
Many people came to the café early in the morning for the beef offal soup, just like me.
# 直接就在这儿吃了
They dine in the café.
# 我先在这儿泡着 那没地方 里面都坐满了
We could hang around here first. No room over there. All seats are taken.
# 关 注
# 雪 鱼  探 店
Follow my channel XUEYU TANDIAN